

DANIEL BATANOV

Experienced professional passionate about building engaging, user-friendly applications. About two years ago, I found a new passion for coding. During that time I worked my skills up through various courses, projects, and internships. My previous experience in Architecture and OA testing has instilled a strong work ethic and a proactive mindset. I am now looking forward to applying my skill set in a new environment alongside like-minded individuals.

🗹 batanoff.s@protonmail.com 📞 0884 044 070 🛭 🛅 LinkedIn 🏶 Website 🕡 Github 🗣 Sofia

PROJECTS

Mini Finance

Book Store

ra-auth-ui

portfolio

EDUCATION BACKGROUND

SoftUni | Web development **UAECG** | Master of Architecture High School of Mathematics | IT

SKILLS

Tech skills

JavaScript ES6+ | HTML5 | CSS | SASS | Tailwind

React | Typescript

NodeJS | Express | Handlebars

Chai | Mocha | Playwright | Jest

MongoDB | Mongoose | (SQL ongoing)

Git | NPM | Yarn | HTTP | REST | AJAX

Soft skills

Problem-solving Growth mindset Motivation

Communication | (Teamwork | Time management

Other skills

3dsMax Photoshop **Figma** Illustrator

CERTIFICATES

Advanced JavaScript Applications JavaScript HTML & CSS

NodeJS Express MongoDB React JS

SQL ongoing

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Frontend Developer Intern

March 2024 - Present Humble Software Ltd

Currently working in the development of a specialized library built on top of React Admin framework, working closely with a technical lead using technologies such as React, TypeScript, React Admin and Material-UI.

Architect

IPA architecture and more 2021 - 2023

Intern Architect

2018 - 2019 Design Art "K&K"

Intern Architect

Integra Consult Project 2017 - 2018

Manual OA

Gameloft 2014 - 2015

- Developed over 100 unique test cases
- Assisted other teams during overtime to resolve major issues
- Consistently giving feedback to developers

ACHIEVEMENTS

Top 10 Softuniada Programming Olympiad

LANGUAGES

English Proficient



Bulgarian Native

